<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="filter_island">Island</string>
    <string name="filter_mainland">Mainland</string>

    <string name="status_alive">Active</string>
    <string name="status_frozen">Frozen</string>
    <string name="status_disabled">Disabled</string>
    <string name="status_appendix_system">System</string>
    <string name="status_appendix_cloned">Cloned</string>
    <string name="status_appendix_exclusive">Exclusive</string>

    <string name="setup_profile_welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="setup_island_intro">\"Island\" is a sandbox environment to clone selected apps and isolate them from accessing your personal data outside (including call logs, contacts and etc) even if permissions are granted.\n\nCloned app runs parallel aside from the installed one with its separate copy of app data. It can also be frozen on demand, with launcher icon vanished and its background behaviors completely blocked.</string>
    <string name="setup_profile_conflict">Android for Work is already set up on your device by \"%1$s\". Due to the limitation of Android system, Island cannot coexist with it. If you proceed, the existent profile WITH ALL ITS DATA WILL BE REMOVED.</string>
    <string name="setup_profile_owner_unknown_app">unknown app</string>
    <string name="setup_button">Build the Island now</string>
    <string name="setup_cleanup_hint">If anything goes wrong during the setup procedure, you can always remove all the data created by Island via \"Settings - Account - Remove work profile\".</string>
    <string name="error_rom_incompatible">Sorry, your device (or ROM) is incompatible with Island.\n\n> %s\n\nPlease refer to the online FAQ for possible solutions.</string>
    <string name="setup_error_managed_profile_not_supported">Sorry, the required feature \"Managed Profile\" is not supported on this device.</string>
    <string name="setup_error_multi_user_not_allowed">Sorry, the required \"Multi-User\" mechanism is disabled on this device.</string>
    <string name="setup_error_provisioning_incomplete">Sorry, the last setup attempt might be unsuccessful, please remove \"Work Profile\" in Account Settings and try again.</string>
    <string name="setup_error_other_work_profile">Sorry, \"Work profile\" was setup on this device already by other app. To use Island, the existent Work Profile must be removed in Account Settings first.</string>
    <string name="error_reason_missing_managed_provisioning">Sorry, the required \"Android for Work\" feature may not be fully supported on your device.</string>

    <string name="tip_empty_app_list">No apps here.\nPlease switch to other view.</string>

    <string name="field_app_id">APP ID: %1$s</string>
    <string name="button_instructions_online">Instructions (online)</string>
    <string name="button_account_settings">Account Settings</string>

    <string name="action_clone">Clone</string>
    <string name="action_clone_back">Clone to mainland</string>
    <string name="action_freeze">Freeze</string>
    <string name="action_unfreeze">Unfreeze</string>
    <string name="action_shortcut">Create launch shortcut</string>
    <string name="action_greenify">Auto-freeze with Greenify</string>
    <string name="action_app_info">App info</string>
    <string name="action_remove">Remove</string>
    <string name="action_uninstall">Uninstall</string>

    <string name="button_create_shortcut">Create launch shortcut</string>
    <string name="button_greenify">Auto-freeze with Greenify</string>
    <string name="button_block">Block</string>
    <string name="button_unblock">Unblock</string>
    <string name="button_remove_clone">Remove clone</string>
    <string name="button_uninstall_clone">Uninstall app</string>
    <string name="button_install_outside">Install outside</string>
    <string name="button_disable_clone">Disable clone</string>
    <string name="button_enable_clone">Enable clone</string>

    <string name="menu_tip">Tip…</string>
    <string name="menu_show_hidden_sys_apps">Show hidden system apps</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_launch_app">Launch app</string>
    <string name="menu_remove_clone">Remove this clone</string>

    <string name="dialog_title_warning">WARNING</string>
    <string name="dialog_manual_setup"><b>For advanced user</b>:\nThis limitation could also be circumvented with one-time manual setup via USB-connected PC.</string>
    <string name="dialog_incompatible_rom">Sorry, your device or ROM does not support \"Managed Profile\" feature, which is required by Island.</string>
    <string name="dialog_encryption_required"><b>DEVICE ENCRYPTION</b> is required on your device to create the island, enforced by Android system. Encrypting the device may degrade the overall performance on some low-end devices. Encryption can be skipped if root privilege is available and granted in the next step.</string>
    <string name="dialog_clone_via_install_explanation">Island will now launch the Android installer to \"install\" this app in Island.\n\nAlthough it looks like the regular installation confirmation, actually it takes no extra storage space but just activates this app in Island. Thus the \"installation\" will finish instantly.</string>
    <string name="dialog_clone_via_google_play_explanation">Island will now launch Google Play Store to clone this app, please then click the \"Install\" button there.\n\nAlthough it will look like the regular installation, actually it will not download the app again and takes no extra storage space but just activates this app in Island. Thus the \"installation\" will finish instantly.</string>
    <string name="dialog_clone_via_sys_market_explanation">Island will now launch the built-in app store on your device to clone this app, please follow the regular installation procedure.\n\nATTENTION: The built-in app store on your device may or may not support Android for Work properly. In case it fails to finish the installation, please refer to the FAQ for solutions.</string>
    <string name="dialog_clone_incapable_explanation">Sorry, Island cannot clone apps without a proper built-in app market on your device (preferable Google Play Store) until Android 5.1. Please refer to the FAQ for solutions.</string>
    <string name="dialog_greenify_title">Greenify integration</string>
    <string name="dialog_greenify_explanation">To save memory and avoid unnecessary battery consumption, Island has no background services in design. Instead it delegates the automatic freezing job to Greenify, taking advantage of its sophisticated automatic hibernation management.</string>
    <string name="dialog_greenify_version_too_low">Greenify needs to be upgraded to a newer version to support Island.</string>
    <string name="dialog_reactivate_message">Island was accidentally deactivated, please grant this manual Device Admin request to re-activate.</string>
    <string name="dialog_destroy_message">Are you sure you want to destroy the whole Island? You will LOSE ALL THE DATA IN ISLAND.\n\nDon\'t worry, apps and data outside Island will NEVER be affected.</string>
    <string name="dialog_destroy_exclusives_message">Since exclusively installed in Island, the following %1$d app(s) will be UNINSTALLED effectively from your device if Island is destroyed.\n\n%2$s\n\nAre you sure you want to proceed?</string>
    <string name="dialog_deactivate_message">Are you sure to deactivate Island?\n\nYou have to go through the setup flow again to bring it back.</string>
    <string name="dialog_cannot_destroy_message">To remove the whole Island space, please open system \"Settings - Accounts\" and select \"Remove work profile\".</string>
    <string name="dialog_add_shortcut">Add a shortcut to de-freeze and launch %1$s?</string>
    <string name="dialog_provision_in_progress">Preparing Island…</string>
    <string name="dialog_never_clone_greenify">Greenify is not supported to run in Island.\n\nIf you want Greenify to freeze app automatically, please use the \"Auto-freeze with Greenify\" action on selected app.</string>

    <string name="dialog_button_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="dialog_button_skip_with_root">Skip (root)</string>
    <string name="dialog_button_learn_more">Learn more</string>
    <string name="dialog_button_install">Install</string>
    <string name="dialog_button_upgrade">Upgrade</string>
    <string name="dialog_button_destroy">Destroy</string>
    <string name="dialog_button_deactivate">Deactivate</string>

    <string name="prompt_disable_sys_app_as_removal">System app can only be disabled. It\'s similar to the removal of an installed app.\n\nIsland has no privilege to do that, instead you will be redirected to the system settings app, there you can click the \"DISABLE\" button to proceed.</string>

    <string name="toast_done">Done</string>
    <string name="toast_setup_completed_and_wait">Setup is complete, please wait for the Island to start.</string>
    <string name="toast_already_cloned">Already cloned</string>
    <string name="toast_shortcut_created">Shortcut created on launcher</string>
    <string name="toast_shortcut_failed">Failed to create the shortcut</string>
    <string name="toast_greenify_failed">Failed to greenify</string>
    <string name="toast_internal_error">Sorry, an internal error occurred, please restart this app and try again.</string>
    <string name="toast_error_freeze_failure">Failed to freeze</string>

    <!-- General words -->
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="setup">Setup</string>
    <string name="open_settings">Open Settings</string>

    <!-- Settings -->

    <string name="settings_title">Settings</string>

    <string name="pref_general_header">General</string>
    <string name="pref_general_launch_shortcut_prefix_title">Launch shortcut prefix</string>

    <string name="pref_privacy_header">Privacy Protection</string>
    <string name="pref_privacy_notification_for_clone_title">Notification of privacy exposure</string>
    <string name="pref_privacy_notification_for_clone_summary">Show notification for potential privacy exposure in cloned apps</string>

    <string name="pref_setup_header">Setup &amp; Shutdown</string>
    <string name="pref_setup_island_title">Island</string>
    <string name="pref_setup_island_summary_managed">Managed</string>
    <string name="pref_setup_island_summary_managed_other">Existent Work profile is not managed by Island.\nClick the side icon to remove.</string>
    <string name="pref_setup_island_summary_incomplete">Setup incomplete.\nClick the side icon to rebuild.</string>
    <string name="pref_setup_island_summary_not_setup">Not setup yet.\nIsland can only be setup manually if mainland is managed, since Android 6.0.\nClick the side icon to open online setup guide.</string>
    <string name="pref_setup_island_summary_pending_setup">Not setup yet.\nClick the side icon to setup.</string>
    <string name="pref_setup_mainland_title">Mainland</string>
    <string name="pref_setup_mainland_summary_managed">Managed</string>
    <string name="pref_setup_mainland_summary_not_managed">Normal</string>
    <string name="pref_setup_category_troubleshooting">Troubleshooting</string>
    <string name="pref_setup_island_reprovision_title">Re-provision Island</string>
    <string name="pref_setup_island_reprovision_summary">This may help to fix issues in Island.\nAll apps and data will be preserved.</string>

    <string name="pref_about_header">About</string>
    <string name="pref_about_version_title">Version</string>
    <string name="pref_about_licenses_title">Licenses</string>

    <!-- New User Guide -->

    <string name="prompt_filter_title">Switch app collection</string>
    <string name="prompt_filter_text">Use the spinner to switch among different collection of apps.\n\nAvailable actions for app may differ.</string>
    <string name="prompt_freeze_title">Freeze app in Island</string>
    <string name="prompt_freeze_text">Once frozen, the app in Island will vanish until being explicit unfrozen.\n\nApp could do absolutely nothing in frozen state.</string>
    <string name="prompt_clone_title">Clone app to Island</string>
    <string name="prompt_clone_text">To apply the magic, app in mainland needs to be cloned into Island first.\n\nThe clone has its own copy of data, but shares the executable binaries with the one in mainland.</string>

</resources>
