<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Island</string>
    <string name="profile_name">Island</string>

    <string name="state_alive">Active</string>
    <string name="state_frozen">Frozen</string>
    <string name="state_disabled">Disabled</string>
    <string name="state_not_cloned">Not cloned</string>
    <string name="status_exclusive">(Exclusive Clone)</string>

    <string name="setup_profile_welcome">Welcome to Island</string>
    <string name="setup_profile_message">We need to open the profile setup page for Island to  create Environment.</string>
    <string name="setup_profile_conflict">Android for Work is already set up on your device by \"%1$s\". Due to the limitation of Android system, Island cannot coexist with it. If you proceed, the existent profile WITH ALL ITS DATA WILL BE REMOVED.</string>
    <string name="name_unknown_app">unknown app</string>
    <string name="setup_button">Create Environment</string>
    <string name="setup_cleanup_hint">If anything goes wrong during the setup procedure, you can always remove all the data created by Island via \"Settings - Account - Remove work profile\".</string>

    <string name="field_app_id">APP ID: %1$s</string>
    <string name="button_create_shortcut">Create launch shortcut</string>
    <string name="button_remove_clone">Remove the clone</string>
    <string name="button_disable_clone">Disable the clone</string>
    <string name="button_enable_clone">Enable the clone</string>

    <string name="menu_show_all_apps">Show all apps</string>
    <string name="menu_remove_clone">Remove this clone</string>
    <string name="menu_destroy_island">Destroy the Island</string>
    <string name="menu_launch_app">Launch app</string>

    <string name="dialog_title_warning">WARNING</string>
    <string name="dialog_clone_via_install_explanation">Island will now launch the Android installer to \"install\" this app in Island.\n\nAlthough it looks like the regular installation confirmation, actually it takes no extra storage space but just activates this app in Island. Thus the \"installation\" will finish instantly.</string>
    <string name="dialog_clone_via_google_play_explanation">Island will now launch Google Play Store to clone this app, please then click the \"Install\" button there.\n\nAlthough it will look like the regular installation, actually it will not download the app again and takes no extra storage space but just activates this app in Island. Thus the \"installation\" will finish instantly.</string>
    <string name="dialog_clone_via_builtin_market_explanation">Island will now launch the built-in app store on your device to clone this app, please follow the regular installation procedure.\n\nATTENTION: The built-in app store on your device may or may not support Android for Work properly. In case it fails to finish the installation, please refer to the FAQ for solutions.</string>
    <string name="dialog_clone_incapable_explanation">Sorry, Island cannot clone apps without a proper built-in app market on your device (preferable Google Play Store) until Android 5.1. Please refer to the FAQ for solutions.</string>
    <string name="dialog_reactivate_message">Island was accidentally deactivated, please grant this manual Device Admin request to re-activate.</string>
    <string name="dialog_destroy_message">Are you sure you want to destroy the whole Island?\n\nYou will LOSE ALL THE DATA IN ISLAND.\n\nApps and data outside Island will NOT be affected.</string>
    <string name="dialog_deactivate_message">Are you sure to deactivate Island?\n\nYou have to go through the setup flow again to bring it back.</string>
    <string name="dialog_destroy_failure_message">Failed to destroy Island. Please try removing it in system \"Settings - Accounts - Remove work profile\".</string>
    <string name="dialog_add_shortcut">Add a launch shortcut for %1$s?</string>
    <string name="dialog_button_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="dialog_button_destroy">Destroy</string>
    <string name="dialog_button_deactivate">Deactivate</string>

    <string name="toast_shortcut_created">Shortcut created on launcher</string>
    <string name="toast_shortcut_failed">Failed to create the shortcut</string>
    <string name="toast_shortcut_invalid">Shortcut is no longer valid, please check the status of Island or re-create it in Island</string>

</resources>
